Guide to the Mark D. Weiser Papers, 1969-1999
Department of Special Collections
- Series 11. Printed material
  - Subseries C: Publications by others
    - Rudofsky, Bernard. Behind the picture window. New York: Oxford Press, 1955 (Box 114, Folder 11)
    - Rumelhart, David (Box 114, Folder 12)
    - Ryall, Kathy. Annotating floor plans using deformable polygons / Kathy Ryall, et al., 1993 (Box 114, Folder 13)
    - Ryder, Barbara (Box 114, Folder 14)
    - Saal, Harry (Box 114, Folder 15)
    - Sakamura, Ken. Ubiquitous computing. Kagaku Asahi, 1995 (Box 114, Folder 16)
    - Sandewall, Erik (Box 114, Folder 17)
    - Sanguinetti, John (Box 114, Folder 18)
    - Satto - Schilit (Box 114, Folder 19)
    - Schank, Robert (Box 114, Folder 20)
    - Schilit, Bill N. As we may read: the reading appliance revolution. IEEE, 1999 Jan. (Box 114, Folder 21)
    - Schober, Robert C. Ultra low power circuit techniques for focal plane electronics applications, 1991 Jan. 6 (Box 115, Folder 1)
    - Schober, Robert C. Ultra low power circuit techniques for focal plane electronics applications, 1992 June 10 (Box 115, Folder 2)
    - Schober, Robert C. Ultra low power circuit techniques for focal plane electronics applications, 1993 July 22 (Box 115, Folder 3)
    - Schuler - Sharma (Box 115, Folder 4)
    - Schwans, Karsten (Box 115, Folder 5)
    - Schwartz, Peter (Box 115, Folder 6)
    - Shaw, Mary. We can teach software better. Computing Research News, 1992 Sept. 4 (Box 115, Folder 7)
    - Shenker - Singh (Box 115, Folder 8)
    - Sheppard, Sylvia (Box 115, Folder 9)
    - Shimizu, Hiroshi. Miscellaneous articles (Box 115, Folder 10)
    - Shneider, Ben (Box 115, Folder 11)
    - Shooman, Martin (Box 115, Folder 12)
    - Sieworek, Daniel (Box 115, Folder 13)
    - Simon, Herbert (Box 115, Folder 14)
    - Sindhu, Pradeep (Box 116, Folder 1)
    - Sitkin - Smith (Box 116, Folder 2)
    - Slater, Leland (Box 116, Folder 3)
    - Smith, Carl (Box 116, Folder 4)
    - Smith, David (Box 116, Folder 5)
    - Smith - Sobalvarro (Box 116, Folder 6)
    - Snir, Marc (Box 116, Folder 7)
    - Snodgrass, Richard (Box 116, Folder 8)
    - Sollins, Karen R. Smart spaces: moving into the future, 1998 July 29 (Box 116, Folder 9)
    - Soloway, Elliot (Box 116, Folder 10)
    - Sony Computer Science Laboratory. Selected technical reports 1988.6~1990.5, 1990 May (Box 116, Folder 11)
    - Sony Computer Science Laboratory. Selected technical reports 1990.5~1992.5, 1992 May (Box 116, Folder 12)
    - Sopko, J. Leslie. A softer technology: Xerox chief scientist seeks "a sense of calmness". Rochester Democrat and Chronicle, 1996 May 1 (Box 116, Folder 13)
    - Sorkin - Strong (Box 116, Folder 14)
    - Sproull, Robert (Box 116, Folder 15)
    - Stavely, Orr (Box 117, Folder 1)
    - Stefik, Mark. Internet dreams. Cambridge, Mass.: MIT Press, 1996 (Box 117, Folder 2)
    - Stefik, Mark. The bit and the pendulum: balancing the interests of stakeholders in digital publishing / by Mark Stefik and Alex Silverman., 1997 Sept. (Box 117, Folder 3)
    - Stefik - Suchman (Box 117, Folder 4)
    - Steinhaus, Carolyn (Box 117, Folder 5)
    - Stephens, Keith. Xerox finally wake up, but is it too late? (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Stewart, Thomas A. Your company's most valuable asset: intellectual capital. Fortune, 1994 Oct. 3 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Straathof, Jeffrey H.. A new UNIX process scheduler benchmarked by a remote terminal emulation tool. M.S. thesis, University of Maryland, 1986 (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Strategic News Service, 1999 Feb. 10 (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Suchman - Sutherland (Box 117, Folder 10)
    - Sussman, Gerald (Box 117, Folder 11)
    - Swartout, William (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Symbolics: 3600 technical summary (Box 117, Folder 13)
    - Tajibnapis, William (Box 117, Folder 14)
    - Tano, Shunichi [speech transparencies], 1995 May (Box 117, Folder 15)
    - Taylor - Tenenbaum (Box 117, Folder 16)
    - Technology Business Research. Rescue for the helpdesk, 1996 Feb. 2 (Box 117, Folder 17)
    - Tennenhouse, David. Virtual infrastructure: ARPA ISAT study, 1995 Oct (Box 117, Folder 18)
    - Tennenhouse, David, et al. (Box 117, Folder 19)
    - Tennent, R.D. (Box 117, Folder 20)
    - Testa, James. Lowered supply and threshold voltage effects on CMOS circuit characteristics., 1995 June (Box 118, Folder 1)
    - Thamsiranunt, Manop. CMOS VCOs for PLL frequency synthesis in GHz .... / Manop Thamsirianunt and Tadeusz A. Kwasniewski., 1995 (Box 118, Folder 2)
    - Thekkath, et al. (Box 118, Folder 3)
    - Thomas, J.C. (Box 118, Folder 4)
    - Thomas, Wes (Box 118, Folder 5)
    - Tognazzini - Toho (Box 118, Folder 6)
    - Tomayako, James E. The personal software process: a practitioner's starter kit., 1997 (Box 118, Folder 7)
    - Tomio - Tramontana (Box 118, Folder 8)
    - Tsichritzis, D. (Box 118, Folder 9)
    - Two ways of reading a philosophy -- and their pitfalls, n.d., tms (photocopy) (Box 118, Folder 10)
    - Ulusoy - Vlahos (Box 118, Folder 11)
    - Ungar, David. Generation scavenging: a non-distributive high performance storage reclamation algorithm. Draft no. 1, 1983 Oct. 14 (Box 118, Folder 12)
    - U.S. Congress. Office of Technology Assessment. Innovation and comercialization of emerging technologies., 1995 Sept. (Box 118, Folder 13)
    - U.S. President's Information Technology Advisory Committee. Information technology research., 1999 Feb. 24 (Box 118, Folder 14)
    - Van Dam, Laura. Here a computer, there a computer, n.d. (Box 118, Folder 15)
    - Voice operated personal command system (VPCS) semi-annual technical report, 1992 Jan. 1 - May 30 (Box 118, Folder 16)
    - Wada - Want (Box 118, Folder 17)
    - Waldo, Jim. Jini architecture overview (Box 118, Folder 18)
    - Walker, Wayne G. Recovering the fumbles and organizing for the future, 1993 (Box 118, Folder 19)
    - Wallace, Richard (Box 118, Folder 20)
    - Want - Wenzel (Box 119, Folder 1)
    - Wegbreit, Ben (Box 119, Folder 2)
    - Weiser, Ann. Conversational strategems: a study in the pragmatics of language. Ph.D. dissertation, University of Chicago, 1975 (Box 119, Folder 3)
    - Weynker - Wiltgen (Box 119, Folder 4)
    - Wheeler, John (Box 119, Folder 5)
    - Whitehead, B. (Box 119, Folder 6)
    - Wild, Helga. Mathematics: a writing praxis / Helga Wild and Niklas Damiris. In Body in places (Box 119, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Dapo. Xerox takes wraps off plan for digital scanning camera. Microscope, 1998 June 2 (Box 119, Folder 8)
    - Winston, Patrick (Box 119, Folder 9)
    - Wolff - Wood (Box 119, Folder 10)
    - Wolkomir, Richard. We're going to have computers coming out of the woodwork. (Box 119, Folder 11)
    - Wood, David A. (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - Wood, Rich (Box 119, Folder 13)
    - Woodfield, S.N. (Box 119, Folder 14)
    - Wortman, David (Box 119, Folder 15)
    - Wulf, William (Box 119, Folder 16)
    - Wyk, Christopher van (Box 119, Folder 17)
    - Youngs, Edward (Box 119, Folder 18)
    - Yamagishi, Akihiro. A 2-V, 2-GHz low-power direct digital frequency ...., 1995 (Box 119, Folder 19)
    - Yokote - Zilsel (Box 119, Folder 20)
    - Yovitz, M.C. (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - Zak, Mary (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - Zeigler, B.P. (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - Zelkowitz, M.V. (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - Zong, Yang Xiao (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - Zorn - Zuboff (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - Zue - Zweig (Box 120, Folder 7)
    - Publications, 1986-1988 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - Publications, 1989 - 1991 May 15 (Box 120, Folder 9)
    - Publications, 1992 Feb. - June 10-11 (Box 120, Folder 10)
    - Publications, 1992 Oct. 1-29 (Box 120, Folder 11)
    - Publications, 1993 Jan. (Box 120, Folder 12)
    - Publications, 1993 Jan. (Box 121, Folder 1)
    - Publications, 1993 Feb. 27 - June (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Publications, 1993 June - July (Box 121, Folder 3)
    - Publications, 1993 Sept. - Dec. (Box 121, Folder 4)
    - Publications, 1993 (Box 121, Folder 5)
    - Publications, 1994 Jan. (Box 121, Folder 6)
    - Publications, 1994 Mar. - Apr. (Box 121, Folder 7)
    - Publications, 1994 June 8 (Box 121, Folder 8)
- Series 12. Xerox documents
  This series contains publications, reports, information packages, and memos published by Xerox and distributed to its employees.
  - Publications: Alto: a personal computer (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Publications: An analysis of a Mesa instruction sheet (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Documents: Annual report, 1994 (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Documents: Annual report, 1995 (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Documents: Annual report, 1996 (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Approximating treewidth, pathwidth, & minimum elimination tree height (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - Arrangement and alliance management empowerment toolkit (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Assessing the key enabling technologies for mobile computing [1 of 4] (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - Assessing the key enabling technologies for mobile computing [2 of 4] (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Assessing the key enabling technologies for mobile computing [3 of 4] (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Assessing the key enabling technologies for mobile computing [4 of 4] (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Benefit [1 of 4] (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Benefit [2 of 4] (Box 123, Folder 1)
  - Benefit [3 of 4] (Box 123, Folder 2)
  - Benefit [4 of 4] (Box 123, Folder 3)
  - C-Cedar / Mesa interoperability / Raymond T. Liu. El Segundo, Calif.: Xerox, 1992 Aug. 7 (Box 123, Folder 4)
  - Cedar 5.2 manual / Xerox PARC Computer Science Laboratory [1 of 5] (Box 123, Folder 5)
  - Cedar 5.2 manual / Xerox PARC Computer Science Laboratory [2 of 5] (Box 123, Folder 6)
  - Cedar 5.2 manual / Xerox PARC Computer Science Laboratory [3 of 5] (Box 123, Folder 7)
  - Cedar 5.2 manual / Xerox PARC Computer Science Laboratory [4 of 5] (Box 123, Folder 8)
  - Cedar 5.2 manual / Xerox PARC Computer Science Laboratory [5 of 5] (Box 123, Folder 9)
  - Publications: The clearinghouse (Box 123, Folder 10)
  - Color gamut mapping & the printing of digital color images / Maureen C. Stone et al. (Box 123, Folder 11)
  - Conversion handbook for Xerox / EDS Personnel, 1996 Jan. (Box 123, Folder 12)
  - Cool lab. One day business college, 1997 Feb. 6 (Box 123, Folder 13)
  - Corporate Research & Technology (Box 123, Folder 14)
  - Customer Focus Group Interviews: administrative and technical support services. Final report, 1991 July (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Developer's guide to XTIP applications, Version 1.0 / Dennis L. Venable. S.l.: Xerox,, 1994 (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Publications: The Ethernet local network (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Publications: Digests of recent research (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Digital imaging technology strategy / William Lama, ed. S.l.: Xerox,, 1997 Jan. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Displaying data structures for interactive debugging (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Do users manual (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Document services architecture: preliminary functional specification, 1993 Apr. 15 (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Ethernet: distributed pocket switching for local computer networks / by Robert M. Metcalfe and David R. Boggs, 1975 Nov. (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Experiences linking customers and research topic selection / Michael Campanelli, et al. Xerox Corp.,, 1995 (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Fact book, 1996 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Formal specification of memory models (Box 125, Folder 5)
  - Implementing long lived transactions using log record forwarding (Box 125, Folder 6)
  - Publications: Interim 3-LISP reference manual (Box 125, Folder 7)
  - Document: Internal memos (Box 125, Folder 8)
  - Document: Internal memos: Proctor & Gamble, 1997 July 31 (Box 125, Folder 9)
  - Publications: Interlisp-D user's guide (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Publications: Internet broadcasting (Box 125, Folder 11)
  - Maintaining the illusion of a functional language in the presence of side effects (Box 125, Folder 12)
  - Mesa language manual (Box 125, Folder 13)
  - A method for reduction of color image-buffer storage with guaranteed printing / by Steven J. Harrington, Stephen C. Morgana. -- Technical report X9200265. S.l.: Xerox,, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 14)
  - Documents: Mid-year repor, 1994 Jan. - June (Box 125, Folder 15)
  - Documents: Miscellaneous flyers (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - NII assumption set from November 17 meeting, 1994 Nov. 28 (Box 126, Folder 2)
  - NII-related Xerox technology and IPs (Box 126, Folder 3)
  - A new approach to imaging IC layout & schematics (Box 126, Folder 4)
  - The new productivity through the document and knowledge medium, 1993 July 5 (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - The optical mouse (Box 126, Folder 6)
  - Organizational charts (Box 126, Folder 7)
  - PARC annual report, 1994 (Box 126, Folder 8)
  - PARC messaging strategy, 1998 Dec. 5 (Box 126, Folder 9)
  - PARC paper for pendery and planning purposes, 1971 June 11 (Box 126, Folder 10)
  - PARC quality organization participant work book [1 of 2] (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - PARC quality organization participant work book [2 of 2] (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - Personal document reader research roadmap / Morgan Price, Bill Schilit, and Gene Golovchinsky. -- 1st ed. -- TR-97-011, 1997 June 16 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Personal dynamic media / Xerox Palo Alto Research Center. Learning Research Group, 1976 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Publications: Plans and situated actions: the problems of human-machine communication (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Publications: Preliminary report on the Larch shared language (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Publications: Printer Quoth (Box 126, Folder 17)
  - Production Systems Group strategy (Box 126, Folder 18)
  - Publications: Publishing Focus newsletter, 1986 July 14 (Box 127, Folder 1)
  - Publications: Pup: an inter network architecture (Box 127, Folder 2)
  - Re:reading / Research in Experimental Doucments (RED), Xerox PARC (Box 127, Folder 3)
  - Publications: Requirements for an experimental programming environment (Box 127, Folder 4)
  - Publications: Safe, effective garbage collection for C++ / by John R. Ellis and David L. Detlefs (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Documents: Scrapper [1 of 3] (Box 127, Folder 6)
  - Documents: Scrapper [2 of 3] (Box 127, Folder 7)
  - Documents: Scrapper [3 of 3] (Box 127, Folder 8)
  - Solving sexual harassment (Box 127, Folder 9)
  - A stylus-based user interface for text: entry and editing (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Time to market (Box 127, Folder 11)
  - Total cost of ownership assessment [1 of 2] (Box 127, Folder 12)
  - Total cost of ownership assessment [2 of 2] (Box 127, Folder 13)
  - Total cost of ownership reduction recommendations (Box 127, Folder 14)
  - Towards "WYSIWYG" color (Box 127, Folder 15)
  - VLSI design aids: capture, integration, & layout generation (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Publications: WFS: a simple shared file system for a distributed environment (Box 128, Folder 2)
  - Xerox and the Internet, 1996 (Box 128, Folder 3)
  - Xerox Corporation (Box 128, Folder 4)
  - Xerox Document Conferencing Unit. Liveboard (Box 128, Folder 5)
  - Xerox Eureka: knowledge sharing that works (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Xerox foundation supported research at UCSB / Peter Hantos. El Segundo, Calif.: Xerox Advanced Technology & Competency Development,, 1993 May 6 (Box 128, Folder 7)
  - Xerox. Industrial design / human interface,, n.d. (Box 128, Folder 8)
  - Xerox PARC [information package], 1997 (Box 128, Folder 9)
  - Xerox PARC [information package], 1997 (Box 128, Folder 10)
  - Xerox PARC. Code of safe practices (Box 128, Folder 11)
  - XeroxWorld. -- Issue no. 4, 1994 (Box 128, Folder 12)
  - XeroxWorld., 1998 Winter (Box 128, Folder 13)
  - You & Xerox (Box 128, Folder 14)
  - You & Xerox: benefits for salaried employees,, 1993 (Box 128, Folder 15)
- Series 13. Photographs
  - Photographs of Mark Weiser (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Photographs of MPad (Box 129, Folder 2)
  - Photographs of Xerox PARC employees (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Photographs of Future Computers (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - Photographs: Miscellaneous (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Photographs: Bali trip, 1998 Feb. 19 (Box 129, Folder 6)
  - Photographs: Reception (Box 129, Folder 7)
  - Photographs: Sky-diving (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Negatives (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - Color slides: Liveboard; PAD (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - Equipment transparencies (colored) (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - Slides (Box 129, Folder 12)
- Series 14. Media materials
  Arranged into four subseries, including Subseries A: Computer diskettes; Subseries B: CD-Roms; Subseries C: Audiocassettes; and Subseries D: Videotapes
  - Subseries A: Computer diskettes
    - Maxi-Pro: programmable KYB software, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 1)
    - MD2, n.d. Apr. 22, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 2)
    - Minder installation disk 1/1, 1996 Nov. 9, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 3)
    - Mudge.notes, 1991 May, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 4)
    - PARC software, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 5)
    - PCR source code, 1989, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 6)
    - PCR source code, 1989, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 7)
    - PGRNEW.IGS, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 8)
    - Rinball, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 9)
    - tar xrf /dev/fd0c 10-14, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 10)
    - Vita3.doc, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 11)
    - Xerox digital templates, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 12)
    - Doom 1, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 13)
    - Doom 2, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 14)
    - Minder installation, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 15)
    - Untitled diskette, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 16)
      Gorgon.trz -- hologram.txt -- Hydra.trz -- Loghost -- Making Web Publications permanent -- Pop3.tgz -- Pop3.trz --Sendmail.cf -- Stuff.trz
    - Untitled diskette, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 17)
      PARC 1-6-99.ppt -- Process presentation.ppt
    - BoundsChecker Standard edition for Windows 95, ver. 3.01. Disk 1, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 18)
    - BoundsChecker Standard edition for Windows 95, ver. 3.01. Disk 2, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 19)
    - BoundsChecker Standard edition for Windows 95, ver. 3.01. Disk 3, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 20)
    - diba product photographs: JPEG format, 1996, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 21)
    - General Parametric Co. VS presenter v2.0, 1994, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 22)
    - General Parametric Co. VideoShow presenter v1.1, 1989, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 23)
    - General Parametric Co. VideoShow presenter v2.2, 1989, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 24)
    - ICQ, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 25)
    - It's in the air: RadioMail connection for Windows, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 26)
    - Mobidem demo program, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 27)
    - Monarch demo for Windows, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 28)
    - New Media Corp. CardSoft card & socket services ver. 3.1, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 29)
    - PC-Install for Windows 95/NT, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 30)
    - PCI mainboard supporting diskette rev. 3.4, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 31)
    - PenPoint software (source) P/N: 232002-1 rev. 1.1, 1991, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 32)
    - PenPoint software development kit v. 1.0a Disk 3, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 33)
    - RocketPort Series driver: SCO OpenServer release 2.02, 1998 Jan. 6, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 34)
    - RocketPort Series diagnostics and EISACFG files release 1.5, 1997 Oct. 20, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 35)
    - RocketPort Series drivers release 1.4, 1997 Oct. 7, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 36)
    - Socket IO installation diskette release 2.10, 1994 May 18, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 37)
    - SPARCbook soft PC ver. 3.05. Disk 1 of 2, 1992 Aug. 5, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 38)
    - SPARCbook soft PC ver. 3.05. Disk 2 of 2, 1992 Aug. 5, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 39)
    - Spectrum ringmouse ver. 1.3.2, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 40)
    - Tanner Research Lights demo, 1995, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 41)
    - Tanner Research demo disk 1 of 2, 1997, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 42)
    - Tanner Research demo disk 2 of 2, 1997, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 43)
    - Timex Datalink Ver. 2 Beta 2, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 44)
    - TPG folio infobase: advanced wireless communications, 1993, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 45)
    - U.S. Robotics Palm Pilot network hotsync for Windows 95, Windows NT 4.0, n.d., 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 46)
    - VersaPoint software ver. 2.0, 1993, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 47)
    - World Economic Forum 1997 interactive members handbook, 1997, 1 computer disk: double sided, high density; 3.5 in. (Box 130, Othertype 48)
  - Subseries B: CD-Roms
    - Geek of the week interview with Cliff Lynch. Kahlonia: /kalonia/weiser, 1993 June 4, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 1)
    - Rossmoore study group: Mark & Carl ISO 9660, 1998 May 27, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 2)
    - Dohatec New Media interactive multimedia applications: Mark Weiser, Chief Technologist, Xerox PARC, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 3)
    - 3Com Corp. Palm III connected organizer, 1996, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 4)
    - Adaptec EZ-SCSI 4.0 software for Windows. -- Ver. 4.01, 1995, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 5)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science. Directory of members, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 6)
    - American Association for the Advancement of Science. Directory of members. c. 2, 1998, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 7)
    - Association for Computing Machinery. Special Interest Group on Operating Systems. Proceedings of the Fifteenth ACM Symposium on Operating Systems Principles. c. 1, 1995 Dec. 3-6, 1 CD-Rom disk (Box 131, Othertype 8)